She wants your children.
The Curse of La Llorona is a horror film directed by Michael Chaves.
In 1970s Los Angeles, the legendary ghost La Llorona is
stalking the night -- and the children.
Ignoring the eerie warning of a troubled mother, a social worker and her
own kids are drawn into a frightening supernatural realm.
Their only hope of surviving La Llorona's deadly wrath is a
disillusioned priest who practices mysticism to keep evil at bay.
Anna Tate-Garcia, played by Linda Cardellini.
Rafael Olvera, played by Raymond Cruz.
Patricia Alvarez, played by Patricia Velásquez.
Chris Garcia, played by Roman Christou.
Samantha Garcia, played by Jaynee-Lynne Kinchen.
La Llorona, played by Marisol Ramirez.
The Curse of La Llorona (also known as The Curse of the Weeping Woman in some markets) is a 2019 American supernatural horror film
directed by Michael Chaves, in his feature directorial debut, and written by Mikki Daughtry and Tobias Iaconis.
Based on the Latin American folklore of La Llorona, the film stars Linda Cardellini, Raymond Cruz, and Patricia Velásquez, and
follows a mother in 1973 Los Angeles who must save her children from a malevolent spirit trying to steal them.
The film was produced by James Wan through his Atomic Monster banner and, though not
considered an installment in the franchise, takes place within The Conjuring Universe.
The Curse of La Llorona premiered at South by Southwest on March 15, 2019, and
was theatrically released in the United States on April 19, 2019.
It received mostly unfavorable reviews but was a surprise success at the box
office, grossing $123.1 million worldwide against a $9 million budget.
The film explores themes of mexico, sibling relationship,
1970s, religion and supernatural, supernatural.
The tone is dark.